Register to The Quincy Porter Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Correspondence, Series I
  - Correspondence with Schools, Universities, etc., I.E
    - New Hampshire. University at Durham (Box 6, Folder 67)
      1965 Jan 20 -- typed letter signed
    - The New School for Social Research (Box 6, Folder 67)
      1933 Sep 27 -- typed letter signed (scrapbook)
      1933 Nov 11 -- typed letter (scrapbook)
    - North Carolina. Agricultural & Technical College at Greensboro (Box 6, Folder 67)
      1960 Feb 5 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      typed letter (scrapbook)
    - Northwestern University (Box 6, Folder 67)
      1960 Jun 23 -- typed letter signed
    - Ohio. University at Athens (Box 6, Folder 67)
      1963 Nov 17 -- autograph letter signed
    - Philadelphia Musical Academy (Box 6, Folder 67)
      1948-1950 -- 7 typed letters signed
      1950-1951 -- 1 brochure
    - Portland, University of (Box 6, Folder 68)
      1950 Jan 25 -- typed letter signed
    - Princeton University (Box 6, Folder 68)
      1949 Jun 30 -- typed letter signed
    - Richmond School of Music (Box 6, Folder 68)
      1950 Oct 1 -- typed letter signed (scrapbook)
    - Rochester, University of (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - Rochester, University of. Eastman School of Music (Box 6, Folder 68)
      1946-1954 -- 3 typed letters signed (1-scrapbook)
      1965 Mar 2 -- typed letter signed from Quincy Porter to above
      1959 Apr 6 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      1955 May 18 -- typed letter (copy) from Eastman School to A. Whitney Griswold
      See also: Howard Hanson
    - Stanford University (Box 6, Folder 68)
      1959 Dec 7 -- typed letter signed
    - Syracuse University. Library (Box 6, Folder 68)
      1964 Jan 3 -- typed letter signed
    - Vassar College (Box 6, Folder 69)
      1933-1948 -- 4 typed letters signed (2-scrapbook)
      1932 Feb 1 -- typed letter
      1932 Feb 4 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      1939 Mar 28 -- typed letter signed from Vassar Cooperative Bookshop
      1965 Apr 27 -- 1 guest list, Vassar dinner
      See also: G.S. Dickinson
    - Washington. University at Seattle (Box 6, Folder 69)
      1944 Mar 14 -- typed letter signed (scrapbook)
    - Western Reserve University (Box 6, Folder 69)
      1937 Jan 28 -- typed letter signed (scrapbook)
      No year Jan 26 -- telegram
    - Westminster Choir School (Box 6, Folder 69)
      1938 Apr 13 -- typed letter signed (scrapbook)
    - Willamette University (Box 6, Folder 69)
      1948 May 12 -- typed letter signed (scrapbook)
    - Wisconsin. University at Madison (Box 6, Folder 69)
      1946 Oct 17 -- typed letter signed
    - Wisconsin. University at Milwaukee (Box 6, Folder 69)
      1963 Nov 20 -- typed letter signed
      1963 Dec 3 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      1963 -- 1 brochure
    - Wykeham Rise (Box 6, Folder 69)
      1966 -- 2 autograph letters signed
      1966 -- 5 typed letters signed
      1966 Feb 22 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Wyoming. University at Laramie (Box 6, Folder 69)
      1951 Jan 4 -- telegram (scrapbook)
    - Wyoming. University at Laramie. Library (Box 6, Folder 69)
      1966 Mar 1 -- typed letter signed
  - Correspondence with Societies, Organizations, Leagues, etc., I.F
    - American Academy of Arts & Letters (Box 7, Folder 70)
      1961 Jan 6 -- typed letter signed
    - American Composers Alliance (Box 7, Folder 70-74)
      1947-1966 -- 21 typed letters signed
      1965 Jan 15 -- typed letter signed (carbon)
      1964 May 21 -- typed letter signed from Quincy Porter to above
      1961-1965 -- 2 typed letters signed (copies) from Quincy Porter to above
      1956-1965 -- 3 typed letters (copies) from Quincy Porter to above
      1950-1963 -- 21 newsletters, memos, forms
      1964 -- 12 newsletters, memos, forms
      1965 -- 11 newsletters, memos, forms
      1966 -- 9 newsletters, memos, forms
      No date -- 1 newsletters
    - Letters from ACA, to: (Box 7, Folder 75)
      - Kohs, Ellis B.
        1966 Apr 8 -- typed letter signed (copy)
      - Morton, Lawrence
        1966 May 6 -- typed letter (carbon)
    - Letters to ACA, from: (Box 7, Folder 75)
      - Broadcast Music, Inc.
        1966 May 5 -- typed letter signed (copy)
      - Childs, Barney
        1966 May 8 -- typed letter signed (copy)
      - Kohs, Ellis B.
        1966 Apr 20 -- typed letter signed (copy)
      - Moe, Henry Allen
        1966 Apr 29 -- typed letter signed (copy)
      - Morton, Lawrence
        1966 -- 2 typed letters signed (copies)
      - Stevens, Halsey
        1966 Apr 11 -- typed letter signed (copy)
      - Wuorinen, Charles
        1966 Apr 17 -- typed letter signed (copy)
      - Weigl, Vally
        1966 May 17 -- typed letter signed (copy)
    - Laurel Leaf introductions for Lawrence Morton and Henry Allen Moe (Box 7, Folder 75)
      2 items
      1 brochure
    - American Composers Alliance. Composers Facsimile Edition (Box 7, Folder 76-78)
      1954-1966 -- 20 typed letters signed
      1964-1965 -- 3 typed letters signed (copies)
      1963 Oct 17 -- card
      1963-1965 -- 16 typed letters signed from Quincy Porter to above
      1964 Aug 22 -- typed letter from Quincy Porter to above
      1962-1964 -- 4 typed letters (copies) from Quincy Porter to above
      1952; 1965 -- 2 mimeo letters to all members
      1952-1965 -- 27 receipt forms
      1956 -- 1 royalty statement
    - American Music Center, Inc. (Box 8, Folder 79)
      1942-1966 -- 11 typed letters signed (1-scrapbook)
      1962 Jul 22 -- typed letter signed (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      1949 Jan 9 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      1949-1966 -- 13 newsletters, minutes, memos
    - American Musical Associates (Box 8, Folder 80)
      1952 Jan 2 -- 1 articles of association
      See also: American Recording Society
    - American Recorder Society. Boston chapter (Box 8, Folder 80)
      1960 Jun 27 -- typed letter signed
      1959-1960 -- 2 publicity material
    - American Recording Society (Box 8, Folder 80)
      1952 Apr 30 -- typed letter signed
      1951 Jan 20 -- 1 articles of association
    - American-Soviet Music Society (Box 8, Folder 80)
      1946-1947 -- 6 typed letters signed (1-scrapbook)
      1947 Apr 16 -- typed letter signed (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      1946 -- minutes
    - American Symphony Orchestra League, Inc. (Box 8, Folder 81)
      1962 Dec 7 -- 1 mimeo letter
      1962 Jan-Feb -- 1 newsletter
      See also: Columbia University. Alice M. Ditson Fund; Seattle Symphony Orchestra; Douglas Moore
    - Bethany Volunteer Fireman's Association (Box 8, Folder 81)
    - The Bohemians (Box 8, Folder 81)
      1937 Jan 3 -- typed letter signed
    - The Buffalo Foundation (Box 8, Folder 81)
      1963 May 22 -- typed letter signed
      1963 Jun 6 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - California. San Quentin Board of Prison Terms & Paroles (Box 8, Folder 81)
      1940 Mar 30 -- typed letter signed (copy) from Quincy Porter to above
    - The Catgut Acoustical Society (Box 8, Folder 81)
      1966 -- 2 typed letters signed
      1966 Jun 1-4 -- 1 program brochure
      See also: Frank Lewin; Series VI (Published Articles)
    - The Century Association (Box 8, Folder 82-83)
      1948 Nov 4 -- typed letter signed (scrapbook)
      1964 Oct 28 -- typed letter signed from Quincy Porter to above
      1958; 1964 -- 2 typed letters (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      1965 -- annual report
      1960-1966 -- 8 rules, regulations; reports
    - The Century Association: Correspondence concerning proposed members (Box 8, Folder 82-83)
      - Alexander, Arthur H.
        1963 Nov 8 -- typed letter signed
      - Bixler, J.S.
        1960 May 11 -- typed letter signed
      - Dello Joio, Norman
        1960 Apr 20 -- autograph letter signed
      - Hyde, James Nevins
        1958 Oct 10 -- autograph letter signed
      - James, Philip
        1960 Apr 25 -- autograph letter signed
      - Kimball, Richard A.
        1964 Mar 11 -- typed letter signed
      - Kirkpatrick, Ralph
        1965 Mar 5 -- typed letter signed from Quincy Porter to above
      - McVey, William M.
        1965; No date -- 2 typed letters signed from Quincy Porter to above
      - Moore, Douglas
        No year Dec 11 -- autograph letter signed
      - Pinney, Alexander
        1960 Mar 1 -- autograph letter signed
        1960-1961 -- 4 typed letters signed
        1961 Jan 6 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - Serkin, Rudolf
      - Snow, Emma Folger
        1960 Apr 18 -- autograph letter signed
      - Walker, Hudson D.
    - The Chamber Music Society of America, Inc. (Box 8, Folder 84)
      1935 Jun 3 -- typed letter signed (scrapbook)
    - Columbia University. Alice M. Ditson Fund (Box 8, Folder 84)
      1962 -- 2 typed letters signed
      1963 Aug 5 -- typed letter signed (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      1947-1956 -- 2 minutes, memos
      See also: American Symphony Orchestra League; Seattle Symphony Orchestra
    - Composers Forum (Box 8, Folder 84)
    - Cummins Engine Co., Inc. (Box 8, Folder 84)
      1966 Mar 10 -- typed letter signed
      1966 Mar 18 -- typed letter signed (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - The Dallas Chamber Music Society, Inc. (Box 8, Folder 84)
      1957 Oct 15 -- autograph letter signed
      1957-1959 -- 6 typed letters signed
      1958 Nov 18 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      1 publicity sheet
    - Davenport, Iowa. Friends of Chamber Music (Box 8, Folder 85)
      1960-1961 -- 5 autograph letters signed
      1961 -- 3 typed letters signed
      1960-1961 -- 7 typed letters (copies) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Ford Foundation (Box 8, Folder 86)
      1959-1962 -- 5 typed letters signed
      1962 -- 2 typed letters signed (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      1959 Mar 31 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      1959-1964 -- 4 expense reports
      1961 Sep 18 -- typed letter (carbon) from Ford Foundation to Basil D. Henning
    - George Gershwin Memorial Foundation (Box 8, Folder 87)
      1957-1959 -- 5 typed letters signed
      1958 Nov 24 -- typed letter signed (copy) from Quincy Porter to above
      1959 -- 2 typed letters (copies) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Gordon Musical Foundation, Inc. (Box 8, Folder 87)
    - Griffith Music Foundation (Box 8, Folder 87)
      1949 -- 2 typed letters signed
    - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation (Box 9, Folder 88-90)
      1928-1965 -- 20 typed letters signed
      1930 Jan 30 -- telegram
      1962-1965 -- 2 typed letters signed (copies) from Quincy Porter to above
      1929 Apr 4 -- 1 certificate of award
      1939-1966 -- 8 mimeo letters, other materials
      1929-1966 -- 12 printed brochures
      1929-1930 -- 1 application form
    - L'Institut National de Radiodiffusion (Box 9, Folder 91)
      1949 Aug 10 -- typed letter signed
    - Institute of International Education (Box 9, Folder 91)
      1949-1960 -- 4 typed letters signed
      1960 Sep 12 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Instituto Interamericano de Musicologia (Box 9, Folder 91)
      1943 Jul 8 -- typed letter signed (copy)
    - International Music Council (Box 9, Folder 91)
      1953 Apr 13 -- typed letter signed
    - International Society for Contemporary Music (Box 9, Folder 91)
      1938 Feb 3 -- autograph letter signed (scrapbook)
      1946-1947 -- 2 typed letters signed
      1947 Apr 17 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - League of Composers (Box 9, Folder 91)
      1935-1944 -- 7 typed letters signed (6-scrapbook)
      No year Mar 29 -- telegram (scrapbook)
    - Library of Congress (Box 9, Folder 91)
      1937-1963 -- 6 typed letters signed (3-scrapbook)
      1935-1945 -- 3 certificates of receipt
      See also: copyright folder, Section G
    - Library of Congress. Elizabeth Sprague Coolidge Foundation (Box 9, Folder 91)
      1943-1965 -- 5 typed letters signed (1-scrapbook)
      1964 Jun 22 -- typed letter signed from Quincy Porter to above
      1965 May 24 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      See also: general correspondence with Mrs. Coolidge
    - Manuscript. The Wrexham Foundation, Inc. (Box 9, Folder 92)
      1964 Oct 1 -- autograph letter signed
      1964 Nov 17 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      9 minutes, newsletters, membership lists
    - Music Educators National Conference (Box 9, Folder 93)
      1963 Oct 22 -- 1 recommendation form
    - Music Teachers National Association (Box 9, Folder 93)
      1946-1947 -- 4 typed letters signed
      1946 -- 2 typed letters signed (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - National Arts Club
      See: Winifred Merrill
    - National Association for American Composers and Conductors (Box 9, Folder 93)
      1939 Feb 13 -- autograph letter signed
      1938 Mar 28 -- typed letter signed (scrapbook)
      1936 Dec 23 -- typed letter (scrapbook)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Native American Composers and Musicians (Box 9, Folder 93)
      1966 Apr 19 -- typed letter signed
    - National Association of Schools of Music (Box 9, Folder 93)
      1948-1954 -- 2 typed letters signed
      1959 Feb -- minutes
    - National Federation of Music Clubs (Box 9, Folder 93)
      1947-1950 -- 3 typed letters signed
      1947 Jan 12 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - National Institute of Arts & Letters (Box 9, Folder 94)
      1943-1965 -- 12 typed letters signed (2-scrapbook)
      1958 Nov 25 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      1964 Oct 19 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter (secretary) to above
      1964-1965; No date -- 7 minutes, reports, etc.
    - National Society of Music and Art (Box 9, Folder 95)
      1946 Dec 13 -- typed letter signed
    - New York Public Library (Box 9, Folder 95)
      1960 Nov 9 -- typed letter signed
    - Ohio Music Teachers Association (Box 9, Folder 95)
      1961 Feb 2 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Olympiads XI. Organisations-Komitee (Berlin) (Box 9, Folder 95)
      1936 Aug 21 -- typed letter signed (scrapbook)
      See also: Series VIII (Medals)
    - Pan American Union (Box 9, Folder 95-96)
      1957-1963 -- 12 typed letters signed
      1958 -- 2 typed letters (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      1958 -- 3 miscellaneous printed material; festival brochure
    - Phi Mu Alpha Sinfonia Fraternity of America (Box 9, Folder 97)
      1957 Jun 12 -- autograph letter signed
    - Philadelphia. The Free Library. Edwin A. Fleischer Music Collection (Box 9, Folder 97)
      1939-1964 -- 4 typed letters signed
      1964 -- 2 typed letters signed (carbon)
      1964 Mar 18 -- typed letter (copy)
      1964 -- 4 typed letters signed from Quincy Porter to above
      1958 May 8 -- typed letter (carbon) from Harold Spivacke to above
    - Piano Teachers Information Service (Box 9, Folder 98)
      1959 Mar 1 -- typed letter signed (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Placement Committee for German & Austrian Musicians
      See: Mark Brunswick
    - The Poetry Center (Box 9, Folder 98)
      1947 -- 2 typed letters signed
    - Pulitzer Prize Board (Box 9, Folder 98)
      1943; 1959 -- 2 typed letters signed
      See also: Section B (Congratulatory Letters)
    - Rhodes Scholarship Selection Committee (Box 9, Folder 98)
      1958 -- 2 letters of recommendation
    - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 9, Folder 98)
      1949 Apr 13 -- typed letter signed
      1949 Mar 14 -- 1 memo
    - Rotary Club of Plymouth, New Hampshire (Box 9, Folder 98)
      1957 Jun 29 -- typed letter signed
    - St. Louis Little Symphony Concerts Association (Box 9, Folder 98)
    - Sigma Alpha Iota Music Fraternity (Box 9, Folder 98)
      1958-1963 -- 6 typed letters signed
      1959-1960 -- 3 typed letters (copies) from Quincy Porter to above
      3 printed material
    - Society for the Publication of American Music, Inc. (Box 9, Folder 99)
      1933-1966 -- 20 typed letters signed (5-scrapbook)
      1942 Apr 2 -- typed letter signed (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      1950; 1965 -- 2 memos
    - Squam Lake Association (Box 9, Folder 100)
      1958 May 12 -- typed letter signed
      1959 Mar 23 -- typed letter signed (carbon)
      1957-1966 -- 5 newsletters, lists, etc.
      1959 Mar 30 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to Mrs. Arthur Hove, Sr.
      1959 Mar 30 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to Rev. Kingsland Van Winkle
    - Tavern Club (Box 9, Folder 100)
      1941 -- 2 typed letters signed (scrapbook)
    - United States of America. Department of State (Box 9, Folder 101)
      1963 Oct 8 -- 1 recommendation form, government grant
    - United States of America. Department of War (Box 9, Folder 101)
      1946 Nov 6 -- typed letter signed (scrapbook)
    - United States of America. Office of War Information (Box 9, Folder 101)
      1942 Nov 19 -- typed letter signed (scrapbook)
    - United States of America. Works Progress Administration. Federal Music Project (Box 9, Folder 101)
      1936-1938 -- 4 typed letters signed (1-scrapbook)
      1937 Mar 24 -- typed letter signed (copy)
      1938 Sep 29 -- telegram (scrapbook)
      1938 -- 2 typed letters (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - United States of America. Works Progress Administration. New York State, District 7 (Box 9, Folder 101)
      1937 Jan 25 -- typed letter signed (scrapbook)
    - United States of America. Works Progress Administration. New York State, District 12 (Box 9, Folder 101)
      1936 Dec 23 -- typed letter signed (scrapbook)
    - United States Information Agency (Box 9, Folder 101)
      1954 Feb 23 -- typed letter signed
    - United States Information Service (Box 9, Folder 101)
      1954 Mar 2 -- typed letter signed
    - Violin, Viola, Violoncello Teachers Guild (Box 9, Folder 101)
      1949 Apr 21 -- autograph letter signed (scrapbook)
    - John Hay Whitney Foundation (Box 9, Folder 101)
      1959 Jul 30 -- typed letter signed
  - Other Business, Financial, Legal Correspondence, I.G
    - Copyright materials (Box 10, Folder 102)
      1958-1966 -- 2 typed letters: Copyright office
      1955 Aug 2 -- 1 acknowledgment of receipt of a notice of use of music on mechanical instruments
      1935-1966 -- 28 certificates of copyright registration
    - Contracts (Box 10, Folder 103)
      - American Composers Alliance
        1944 Jun 26 -- 1 item
      - ACA. Composers Facsimile Edition
        1952 Mar 3 -- 1 item
      - American Recording Society
        1951 Jan 22 -- 2 item
      - American Wind Symphony
        1958 Feb 5 -- 1 item
      - Arrow Music Press, Inc.
        1939-1942 -- 2 item
      - Associated Music Publishers, Inc.
        1949-1957 -- 4 item
    - Contracts (Box 10, Folder 104)
      - Boosey & Hawkes, Inc.
        1962 Oct 2 -- 1 item
      - Boston Music Company
        1943 Jan 6 -- 1 item
      - Cleveland Institute of Music
        1931 [May 8?] -- 1 item
      - Columbia Phonograph Company
        1936 Jan 1 -- 1 item
      - Eastman School of Music
        1932 Jul 14 -- 1 item
      - Gamble Hinged Music Co., Inc.
        1946 May 16 -- 1 item
      - H.W. Gray Company, Inc.
        1944-1966 -- 3 item
      - Lima Symphony Orchestra
        1962 Oct 3 -- 1 item
      - Mercury Music Corp. (sample)
        1 item
      - Merion Music, Inc.
        1956 Dec 13 -- 1 item
      - Music Press, Inc.
        1941-1949 -- 4 item
    - Contracts (Box 10, Folder 105)
      - New Haven Symphony Orchestra
        1959 Mar 18 -- 1 item
      - C.F. Peters Corp.
        1958-1963 -- 8 item
      - Society for the Publication of American Music
        1934-1950 -- 3 item
      - Vassar College
        1932-1933 -- 2 item
      - Yale University. Dramatic Association
        1957 Mar 3 -- 1 item
    - Allied Recording Products Co. (Box 10, Folder 106)
      1936-1939 -- 2 typed letters signed
    - Artia-Parliament Industries, Inc. (Box 10, Folder 106)
      1962 Jun 18 -- typed letter signed
    - Associated Hospital Service Corp. (Box 10, Folder 106)
      1939 May 19 -- typed letter signed
      1939 May 25 -- typed letter from Quincy Porter to above
    - Automobile Mutual Insurance Company of America (Box 10, Folder 106)
      1938-1939 -- 3 typed letters signed
      1938 Dec 16 -- 2 rate quotation forms
      1 policy
    - Bromley & Company, Inc. (Box 10, Folder 106)
      1949 Nov 15 -- typed letter signed
    - The Brush Development Company (Box 10, Folder 106)
      1946 Nov 4 -- typed letter signed
      1 invoice
    - Connecticut General Life Insurance Co. (Box 10, Folder 107)
    - Eastman Kodak Company (Box 10, Folder 107)
      1962-1964 -- 2 typed letters signed (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      1962 Aug 30 -- 1 invoice
    - Farmers & Manufacturers National Bank (Box 10, Folder 107)
      1938 Oct 7 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Fiduciary Trust Company (Box 10, Folder 108-109)
      1942-1949 -- 8 typed letters signed
      1956-1959 -- 13 typed letters signed
    - Fiduciary Trust Company (Box 10, Folder 110-114)
      1960-1966 -- 11 typed letters signed
      1964-1966 -- 4 typed letters signed (copies) from Quincy Porter to above
      1955-1966 -- 3 typed letters (copies) from Quincy Porter to above
      1955; 1957 -- 2 annual account reports
      1942-1958 -- 11 principal & interest statements
      1959-1966 -- 7 principal & interest statements
      1954-1957 -- 4 account analysis & appraisal sheets
      1949-1966 -- 12 memos
      1949-1964 -- 10 duplicate brokers statements
    - Holderness, New Hampshire. Board of Assessors, Selectmen (Box 10, Folder 115)
      1947 Sep 11 -- typed letter signed (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - William M. Hotchkiss Company (Box 10, Folder 115)
      1965 Nov 10 -- typed letter signed
    - Iberia Air Lines (Box 10, Folder 115)
      1964 Oct 7 -- typed letter signed from Quincy Porter to above
    - Liberty Mutual Insurance Companies (Box 10, Folder 115)
      1950 Jun 7 -- 1 statement
      1950 May 24 -- 1 rate change endorsement
      1950 May 24 -- 1 reinstatement of insurance form
    - Moses Radio-Electronics Company (Box 10, Folder 115)
      1956 May 16 -- autograph letter signed
      1951-1952 -- 2 typed letters signed
    - Music Print Corporation (Box 10, Folder 116-117)
      1957-1965 -- 11 typed letters signed
      1960-1962 -- 3 typed letters from Quincy Porter to above
      1958 May 15 -- 1 newsletter
      2 brochures
      2 musicwriter instruction manuals
    - New England Telephone & Telegraph Co. (Box 10, Folder 118)
      1950 Mar 15 -- typed letter signed
    - New Haven Savings Bank (Box 10, Folder 118)
      1949 Aug 19 -- 1 statement
    - North American Lamp Company (Box 10, Folder 118)
      No date -- typed letter signed from Quincy Porter to above
      1962 -- 2 typed letters signed from Peter F. Pasbjerg & Co, Inc.
      1962 -- 2 typed letters (copies) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Joseph Settin (Box 10, Folder 118)
      1937 Dec 20 -- 1 receipt
      2 typed letters signed from Peter F. Pasbjerg & Co, Inc.
      2 typed letters (copies) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Sonocraft Corporation (Box 10, Folder 118)
      1950 Jan 26 -- typed letter signed
    - Squam Boats, Inc. (Box 10, Folder 118)
      1965 Mar 27 -- autograph letter signed
      1965 Mar 25 -- typed letter (copy) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association (Box 10, Folder 118)
      1965 Feb 24 -- typed letter signed (copy) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Wheelock Signals, Inc. (Box 10, Folder 118)